#### **PRIVACY POLICY of Rapid VPN**

Welcome to the website and online services of Rapid VPN, as provided by DuoPeak LLC. ("Rapid VPN," "we", or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how information about you or associated with you ("personal information") is collected, used, and disclosed by Rapid VPN and its affiliates, which own and operate Rapid VPN. This Privacy Policy applies to our websites, including and our mobile apps for iOS, Android, Amazon, and Windows mobile devices (collectively, "our Service").

By accessing or using our Service, you signify that you have read, understood and agree to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE ANY PART OF THE SERVICE PROVIDED.

**Table of Contents**

1. Information we collect and use
2. Sharing Information
3. Your choices regarding your information
4. Security and Storage of Information
5. Persons under the age of 13
6. Links to Third Party websites
7. Your rights and how to access, update, and manage your personal information
8. International Transfers of your personal information
9. Updates to this Policy
10. Contact Us
11. Last Revision Date
12. Developer Information

​

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our collection and use of information, please contact us as at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com.

**1\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND USE**

Our app fully complies with local laws and regulations. We do not support or encourage bypassing geo-restrictions or content limitations.  

The personal information we collect or have about you will either be provided by you directly, come from other sources, or will be collected from your activity on our website or applications and use of the Service as set out below. We collect personal information from our users in order to provide you with a personalized, useful, and efficient experience. The categories of information we collect can include:

**Information you provide**

​

**Registration information**

​

You may use the Service without providing any personal information, but you may choose to associate a Google account to retain and transfer access to VIP content. You can register with us by using Google Connect or other application authentication options to create an account or profile within the Service. All affiliated account information is processed by the authenticator (such as Google Play) and is not stored or used by us.

 ​​

**Payment information**

​

We will also collect some purchase information (which consists of transaction history, including what you have purchased, the price, and the date). Note that your in-app purchase transactions are processed by third-party payment processors, such as Google (for purchases on Android devices) or Amazon (for purchases on Kindle devices). These third-party payment processors do not share your financial information, like credit card numbers, with us.

**Customer Support Correspondence**

​

When you ask for assistance from our Customer Support team, we will collect and store:

●      Your name and e-mail address if provided;

●      Information about your activity on the Service;

●      Information about the status of our Service on the device from which you contact Support (date of installation, most recent update, current version, etc)

●      Your user name or ID number; and

●      Any correspondence connected to the assistance provided to you

​

**Data collected through the use of the Service**

​

If you access the Service on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, including emulators and tablets, we collect the following information about you, to the extent it is available:

​

●       **Usage information.** We collect information about how you interact with our services, such as how much bandwidth you use, and when and for how long you use our services.

●        **Device information.** We collect information from and about the device you use to access our services. For example, we may collect device identifiers, browser types, device types and settings, operating system versions, mobile, wireless, and other network information (such as internet service provider name, carrier name and signal strength), and application version numbers.

●       **Diagnostic information.** We may collect information about the nature of the requests that you make to our servers (such as what is being requested, information about the device and app used to make the request, timestamps, and referring URLs). However, we do not log any information that associates your identity with your VPN browsing activity. We do not maintain any records that show what you were browsing or accessing through a VPN connection.

●       **Location information.** We may collect your location information based on a variety of sources, such as your device’s GPS or by calculating an approximate latitude and longitude based on your IP address.

How to use the data we collected.

 We use the information we collect for various purposes described below.

●      **To provide, maintain, troubleshoot, and support our services.** We use your information for this purpose on the basis that it is required to fulfill our contractual obligations to you. Examples: using information about how much bandwidth you use and how long you use our services in order to provide the services in accordance with a plan to which you have subscribed; using threat and device information to determine whether certain items pose a potential security threat; using location information to connect you to the nearest and fastest VPN server; and using usage information to troubleshoot a problem you report with our services and to ensure the proper functioning of our services.

●      **For billing and payment purposes.** We use your information in order to perform billing administration activities and process payments, which are required to fulfill our contractual obligations.

●      **To communicate with users and prospective users.** We use your information to communicate with you, including by responding to your requests, and sending you information and updates about our services. We may do this in order to fulfill our contract with you, because you consented to the communication, or because we have a legitimate interest in providing you with information about our services.

●      **To improve our services.** We want to offer you the best services and user experiences we can, so we have a legitimate interest in continually improving and optimizing our services. To do so, we use your information to understand how users interact with our services. Examples: we analyze certain usage, device, and diagnostic information to understand aggregated usage trends and user engagement with our services (and, for example, invest in technical infrastructure to better serve regions with increasing user demand); we may use device and threat information to conduct spam, threat, and other scientific research to improve our threat detection capabilities; we review customer feedback to understand what we could be doing better.

●      **To develop new services.** We have a legitimate interest in using your information to plan for and develop new services. For example, we may use customer feedback to understand what new services users may want.

●      **To market and advertise our services.** We may use your information to provide, measure, personalize, and enhance our advertising and marketing based on our legitimate interest in offering you services that may be of interest. Examples: we may use information such as who or what referred you to our services to understand how effective our advertising is; we may use information to administer promotional activities such as sweepstakes and referral programs. Our VPN products do not use your VPN browsing activity for these purposes and we do not maintain any records that show what you were browsing or accessing through a VPN connection.

●      **To prevent harm or liability.** We may use information for security purposes (such as to investigate security issues or to monitor and prevent fraud) and to prevent abuse. We may do this to comply with our legal obligations, to protect an individual’s vital interests, or because we have a legitimate interest in preventing harm or liability to us and our users. For example, we may use account, usage, and device information to determine if an entity is engaging in abusive or unauthorized activity in connection with our services.

●      **For legal compliance.** We internally use your information as required by applicable law, legal process, or regulation. To learn about our practices regarding _sharing_ your information with third parties for legal compliance purposes, see Section 3.1 below. We also use your information to enforce our legal rights and resolve disputes.

**Information we receive from third party sites.**

When you interact with our site through various social media platforms, such as when you login through Google, or another third party service, or share Rapid VPN content on Facebook, Twitter or other sites, we may receive information from the social network including:

​

●      Your profile information

●      Profile picture

●      Gender

●      User name

●      User ID associated with your social media account

●      Age range

●      Language

●      Country

●      Friends list

●      and any other information you permit the social network to share with third parties.

The data we receive is dependent upon your privacy settings with the social network, and we will not post information about you on third party social media sites without your consent. You should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our website or Service.

We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service, as well as to communicate directly with you, such as to send you email messages and push notifications, and permit you to communicate with others on the Service or on social media or invite others to join the Service. We may combine information internally across different Service offerings or games to enhance your experience with our Service.

We may also send you Service-related emails or messages (e.g., account verification, account status, change or updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). For more information about your communication preferences, see "Your Choices Regarding Your Information" below.

**Use of cookies and other technology to collect information.**

To provide our games, websites and interest-based advertising, we use ad identifiers, cookies and similar technologies. This section describes our use of these technologies and how you can manage your preferences.

​

**How do ad identifiers, cookies, and similar technologies work?**

Ad identifiers are non-permanent identifiers such as the Android advertising ID and/or Apple’s ID for advertising (the ‘IDFA’), which are uniquely associated with your device. Similar technologies include tracking pixels within ads. Cookies are small text files that are stored by your browser on your desktop computer or mobile device.

​

When you access the Service, we collect certain technical information in order to (i) analyze the usage of our sites and Service; (ii) provide a more personalized experience; and (iii) manage advertising. We and service providers acting on our behalf, such as Google Analytics, will use Log Files and other tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information over time and across different websites following your use of the Service, including cookies, WiFi information, IP addresses, device type, device identifiers, browser types, browser language, referring and exit pages, and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, Service state and the date and time of activity on our Services, and other similar information. In some cases, we will associate this information with your user ID number for our internal use.

**Do Not Track Disclosure.**

Our Service currently does not respond to “Do Not Track” (DNT) settings in your web browser and operates as described in this Privacy Policy whether or not a DNT signal is received. If we do so in the future, we will describe how we do so in this Privacy Policy. For further details regarding DNT, visit donottrack.us.

​

We also employ other technologies including (i) web beacons, which allow us to know if a certain page was visited or whether an e-mail was opened; (ii) tracking pixels, which allow us to advertise more efficiently by excluding our current users from certain promotional messages, identifying the source of a new installation or delivering ads to you on other websites; and (iii) local shared objects also known as flash cookies, which help us to prevent fraud, remember your in-Service preferences and speed up load times.

​

**How to adjust your preferences for interest-based advertising**

You can choose to prevent your device’s ad identifier being used for interest-based advertising, or you can reset your device’s ad identifier, by changing the settings of your device. Settings vary from device to device but you will usually find the ad identifier settings under “privacy” or “ads” in your device’s settings.

​

You can set your web browser to warn you about attempts to place cookies on your computer or limit the type of cookies you allow. Flash cookies operate differently than browser cookies and cookie management tools available in a web browser may not remove flash cookies. To learn more about and manage flash cookies you can visit adobe.com and make changes at the privacy settings panel. If you disable cookies, you may lose some of the features and functionality of playing our Services, as cookies are necessary to track and enhance your Service activities. Please note that companies delivering advertisements in our Services or on our websites may also use cookies or other technologies, and those practices are subject to their own policies.

​

We also use Google Analytics, who uses cookies to help the website analyze how users use the Service and enhance your experience when you use the Service. For more information on how Google uses this data when you visit our Site or use our Services, visit [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/,](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/,) and to opt out of Google Analytics, visit [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

​

The NAI (Network Advertising Initiative) allows for the central opting out of all its members’ cookies from a single opt-out page. If you prefer not to receive relevant advertising on web pages, please visit the following link: networkadvertising.org/choices/. If you delete your cookies, use a different browser or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.

​

**2\. SHARING INFORMATION**

We may share your personal information in the instances described below. For further information on your choices regarding your information, see the "Your Choices Regarding Your Information" section afterward.

​

**We may share your personal information with:**

​

**Other brands owned or controlled by Rapid VPN**

This includes other companies owned by or under common ownership as Rapid VPN, which also includes our subsidiaries (i.e., any organization we own or control) or our ultimate holding company (i.e., any organization that owns or controls us) and any subsidiaries it owns. These companies will use your personal information in the same way as we can under this Policy.

​

We will share your personal data with our Affiliates including in the United States. Please be aware that the US and other jurisdictions may have a lower standard of data protection laws than your own jurisdiction. We will also share your personal data with third party recipients (i.e., parties other than Rapid VPN) including outside the European Economic Area, in the following circumstances:

​

**Third parties at your request**

For example, you may have the option to share your activities on Rapid VPN with your friends through email, text or on various social media sites.

Third party service providers

We provide your information to third party recipients. These categories of recipients include:

​

●      Hosting providers to store the personal data you provide and for disaster recovery services, as well as for the performance of any contract we enter into with you;

●      Email delivery providers that provide us with email delivery services;

●      Advertisers, ad exchanges and other ad technology companies that require the data to select and serve our relevant advertisements to you and others, and assist us in our marketing efforts;

●      Data analysis providers including Google Analytics that assist us in the improvement and optimization of the websites and apps, and data analysis.

We direct all such third party recipients to maintain the confidentiality of the information disclosed to them and to not use your information for any purpose other than to provide services on our behalf.

​

**Sale or Merger**

In the event that the Company undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may transfer all of your information, including personal data, to the successor organization in such transition.  In such a case, we will first notify you in accordance with local law requirements, if any, regarding those items of personal data that will be transferred, the name and contact details of the recipient, and inform you of how you can withdraw consent thereto.

​

**Safety, security and compliance with law**

Your information, and the contents of all of your online communications (including without limitation chat text, voice communications and IP addresses) may be accessed and monitored as necessary to provide the Service and may be disclosed: (i) when we have a good faith belief that we are required to disclose the information in response to legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena); (ii) to satisfy any applicable laws or regulations; (iii) where we believe that the Service is being used in the commission of a crime, including to report such criminal activity or to exchange information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; (iv) when we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the health and/or safety of you, another person or the public generally; and (v) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Rapid VPN, its users or the public as required or permitted by law and (vi) detect, prevent or otherwise address criminal (including fraud or stalking), security or technical issues.We are fiercely protective of the privacy of our users. For our VPN products, we protect your privacy by ensuring that we do not log or record online activities that you conduct over a VPN connection in any way that can be tied back to you, meaning that we do not have any data to share with law enforcement and government agencies who make requests for information about what you were doing through a VPN connection. Subject to the foregoing, we may share your information if we are required to do so by applicable law; to comply with our legal obligations; to comply with legal process; and to respond to valid law enforcement requests relating to a criminal investigation, or alleged or suspected illegal activity that may expose us, you, or any of our other users to legal liability. If we share your information for these purposes, we limit the information shared to what is legally necessary, and challenge information requests that we believe are unlawful, overbroad, or otherwise invalid.

​

We may also share information with others in an aggregated and anonymous form that does not reasonably identify you directly as an individual.

**3\. YOUR CHOICES REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION**

**Push Notifications**

We may occasionally send you push notifications through our mobile applications to send you game updates, high scores, and other service related notifications that may be of importance to you. You may at any time opt-out from receiving these types of communications by turning them off at the device level through your settings.

​

**Marketing Communications**

If you do not wish to receive promotional emails, you can click the "unsubscribe" button on promotional email communications. Note that you are not permitted to unsubscribe or opt-out of non-promotional messages regarding your account, such as account verification, changes or updates to features of the Service, or technical and security notices.

​

**Online Advertising**

We may permit third party online advertising networks, social media companies, and other parties to collect information about your use of our website and apps over time so that they may play or display ads that may be relevant to your interests on our Service as well as on other websites or apps. Typically, the information we share is provided through cookies or similar tracking technologies.

The only way to completely "opt out" of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser's or mobile device's technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, you may wish to visit  and/or the Network Advertising Initiative's online resources, at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). If you access our service on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through settings.

​

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to delete or anonymize your User Content or Personal Information, please see the section below regarding "Methods of accessing or controlling your information" for more details.

**4\. SECURITY AND STORAGE OF INFORMATION**

Rapid VPN cares about the security of your information and uses commercially reasonable physical, administrative, and technological safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of all information we collect and that we share with our service providers. However, no security system is impenetrable and we cannot guarantee the security of our systems 100%. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Rapid VPN or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which the Company or its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

**5\. PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 13**

The Service and its content are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit any personal information from children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to register for or use the Service. Children under the age of 13 should not use our Service or send us any personal information about themselves at any time. In the event we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal information from children under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information collected from a child under 13, please contact us at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com.

**6\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

The Services may contain links to and from third party websites of our business partners, advertisers, social media sites, and our users may post links to third party websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies. Please check the individual policies before you submit any information to those websites.

**7\. HOW TO ACCESS, UPDATE, AND MANAGE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

**Information we receive from a social networking site (“SNS”)**

To manage the information Rapid VPN receives about you from an SNS where you use our Services, you will need to follow the instructions at that site for updating your information and changing your privacy settings.

●      The privacy management tools for applications on Apple can be found at [http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/.](http://www.apple.com/privacy/manage-your-privacy/)

●      The privacy management tools for Google can be found at [https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/.](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/everyone/start/)

●      The privacy management tools for Amazon can be found at [https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/.](https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/data-privacy-faq/)

You can also manage certain aspects of information collection and use by going to the settings of your (mobile) device and reviewing the permissions of each application.

​

Once Rapid VPN receives your information from an SNS, that information is stored and used by Rapid VPN in accordance with this Privacy Policy, and you may access and update that information as described below. Service or other accounts created with Rapid VPN are considered active until we receive a user request to delete them.

​

**Methods of accessing or controlling your information**

If you no longer want Rapid VPN to make active use of your information, you may send an e-mail to rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com. Place "Delete My Account" in the subject line and include your first name, last name, e-mail address, and user ID number from which you access our Services (if applicable) in the body of the e-mail.  IMPORTANT: If you do so, you will no longer have access to the account or services associated with your account. Should you wish to delete your account, we also recommend disassociating your Google account from our application and removing the application from your mobile device.

Please note that if you ask us to delete your account, you will no longer have access to the account, and all data will be lost and we will not be able to restore it in the future. We will respond to your request within thirty (30) days. Rapid VPN may use your information unless and until you send Rapid VPN such a request.

Please note that your information, for example those records pertaining to payments or customer service matters, may be retained for legal and accounting purposes. If you have sent or posted content on the Service, we may not be able to delete it.

​

●      If you wish to review, change or correct the information we have about you, e-mail us at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com

●      You can turn off push notifications and local notifications by visiting the “notifications” page within the relevant Service.

●      If you have additional questions about this Privacy Policy, contact us at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com

**European Countries Users’ Rights**

If you are located in a country in the European Union, the European Economic Area, or Switzerland, you have certain rights in relation to the personal data we hold about you, which we detail below, and which are subject to exemptions under applicable data privacy laws. Some of these only apply in certain circumstances as set out in more detail below. We also set out how to exercise those rights. Please note that we may require you to verify your identity before responding to any requests to exercise your rights. We will respond to a request by you to exercise those rights without undue delay and at least within one month (although this may be extended by a further two months in certain circumstances). To exercise any of your rights, please send an email to rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com.

​

We may decline to process requests in certain circumstances, such as where requests are manifestly unfounded or excessive or requests that jeopardize the privacy of others.

●      **Deletion of your personal data**

○      In some circumstances, you may request that we erase some of the personal data we hold about you. Should you wish to have your personal information deleted, please contact us at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com. Please provide as much detail as possible on your reasons for the request to assist us in determining whether you have a valid basis for erasure. Please note that in order to process your request you must delete our games from your mobile devices and clear our cookies from any device where you have played our games. When we delete any information, it will be deleted from our active databases but may remain in our archives. Please note, however, we may still retain some or all of that information for other purposes such as maintaining financial records, protecting or enforcing legal rights, maintaining marketing suppression lists or for technical reasons such as maintaining technical security or our database integrity. We may also retain your information in an anonymized form.

●      **Access and portability.**

○      You have a right to know what information we hold about you and in some cases to have the information communicated to you. If you wish to exercise this right please contact us at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com and let us know that you wish to exercise your right of access and what information in particular you would like to receive. Please note that we may not be able to provide all the information you ask for, for instance if the information includes personal information about another person. In some circumstances, you may request the data we process based on consent or to perform our contract with you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format or to request we transfer such personal data to another party. Your rights are subject to exemptions under applicable data privacy laws. If you wish for us to transfer the personal data to another party, please ensure you detail that party and note that we can only do so where it is technically feasible. We are not responsible for the security of the personal data or its processing once received by the third party. We also may not provide you with certain data if providing it would interfere with another’s rights (e.g. where providing the personal data we hold about you would reveal information about another person or our trade secrets or intellectual property) as permitted under applicable data protection rights.

●      **Correction**

○      ​You have the right to correct any personal data held about you that is inaccurate. Where you request correction, please explain in detail why you believe the personal data we hold about you to be inaccurate or incomplete so that we can assess whether a correction is required.

●      **Restriction of processing to storage only**

○      ​You have a right to require us to stop processing the personal data we hold about you other than for storage purposes in certain circumstances, e.g. whilst we are considering whether it should be corrected or deleted or, based on your objection, whether we should permanently stop processing. Please note, however, that if we stop processing the personal data, we may use it again if there are valid grounds for us to do so (e.g. for the defense of legal claims or for another’s protection).

●      **Objection**

○      You have the right to object to our processing of data about you other than where required to perform under the Terms of Use, e.g. in order to send you promotions and special offers marketing. You also have the right to object to our processing of data about you by emailing us at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com in the following circumstances:

■      We are processing the data we hold about you on the basis of our legitimate interest and you object to such processing.  Please provide us with detail as to your reasoning so that we can assess whether there is a compelling overriding interest in us continuing to process such data or we need to process it in relation to legal claims.

■      We are processing the data on the basis of historical/scientific research or statistics and you have a particular reason to object. Your right would not apply where we have been tasked with and it is necessary for us to undertake such processing in the public interest.

■      Complaints: In the event that you wish to make a complaint about how we process your personal data, please contact us in the first instance at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com and we will endeavor to deal with your request. This is without prejudice to your right to launch a claim with the data protection supervisory authority in the EU country in which you live or work where you think we have infringed data protection laws.

**California Residents**

This section applies only to California residents. It describes how we collect, use and share Personal Information of California residents in operating our business, and their rights with respect to that Personal Information. For purposes of this section, “Personal Information” has the meaning given in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) but does not include certain de-identified or aggregated information, information publicly available in government records, or certain information excluded from the CCPA’s scope.

​

Your California privacy rights. Effective January 1, 2020, as a California resident, and upon your verifiable consumer request, you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases we may decline your request as permitted by law.

​

●      Information. You can request the following information about how we have collected and used your Personal Information during the past 12 months: the categories of Personal Information that we have collected; the categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information; the business or commercial purpose for collecting and/or selling Personal Information; the categories of third parties with whom we share Personal Information.

●      Access. You can request a copy of the Personal Information that we have collected about you during the past 12 months.

●      Deletion. You can ask us to delete the Personal Information that we have collected from you. Note that there are a number of exceptions, and we need certain types of information so that we can provide our Services to you. If you ask us to delete some or all of your information, you may no longer be able to access or use the Services.

●      Nondiscrimination. You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discriminatory practices prohibited by California law.

​​

Exercising your rights. You may exercise your California privacy rights described above by emailing us at rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com, or by contacting us via the “Contact Us” link on the game website, or from your game account.

​

We will need to confirm your identity and California residency to process your requests to exercise your information, access or deletion rights. We cannot process your request if you do not provide us with sufficient detail to allow us to understand and respond to it.

​

Response Timing. We aim to respond to a consumer request for access or deletion within 45 days of receiving that request. If we require more time, we will inform you of the reason and extension in writing.

​

Personal Information that we collect, use and share. We describe the sources from which we collect Personal Information and the business and commercial purposes for which we collect this information in Section 1 (INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND USE) and Section 2 (SHARING INFORMATION) above.

​

We do not sell your Personal Information to third parties. We do share Personal Information with third parties for the business and commercial purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including without limitation advertising and marketing of our Services.

**8\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

As you are contracting for the Services with Rapid VPN, which is a US company, any information you provide to us, or that we collect through your use of the Services that is necessary to provide you the Services, will be stored, processed, and transferred within, or to, the United States. As a result, your information could be accessed by foreign governmental authorities, or otherwise, in accordance with applicable local laws.

​

Please be aware that the US and jurisdictions other than the one in which you are located will not have the same data protection laws as your own jurisdiction.

​

Your personal data is also processed by staff or service providers operating outside the EEA in the United States, who work for us.  If we transfer your information outside of your country of residence, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**9\. UPDATES TO THIS POLICY**

We reserve the right to modify this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Revision" date below and will post the updated Policy on this page. If you object to any changes, you may close your account. Continuing to use our Services after we publish changes to this Privacy Policy means that you are consenting to the changes.

**10\. CONTACT US**

If you have questions about this Policy, please contact us at [rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com](mailto:rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com)

**11\. LAST REVISION DATE**

This Policy was last revised on, and effective as of March 22, 2023

**12\. Developer Information**

Developer name: DuoPeak Inc

Email address: rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com

​

**REGION-SPECIFIC ADDENDUM TO PRIVACY POLICY:**

The following additional information applies, and supplements the above Privacy Policy, if your personal information is collected from one of the countries below:

**Australia**

You can opt out of receiving commercial electronic messages (such as emails) from us at any time by contacting rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com. Your consent to disclosure outside Australia under this policy means that we will not be accountable to you under the Privacy Act for acts and practices of recipients outside Australia.

**Canada**

Personal information maintained and processed by us and third party service providers in the U.S. and other foreign jurisdictions may be subject to disclosure pursuant to a lawful access request by U.S. or foreign courts or government authorities. We will not provide your information to third parties for marketing purposes without your prior consent.

For more information about our privacy practices; to access, update or correct inaccuracies in your personal information; or if you have a question or complaint about the manner in which we or our service providers treat your personal information, please contact rapidvpn.cs@gmail.com.

**Japan**

We comply with Japanese laws and regulations, including the Act on the Protection of Personal Information (the “PIPA”). For more information on what information Google collects and how it uses this data, go to [https://www.google.com/intl/ja/policies/privacy/.](https://www.google.com/intl/ja/policies/privacy/) If you prefer not to receive relevant advertising on web pages, please follow the instructions provided by Google at [https://www.google.com/intl/ja/policies/privacy/.](https://www.google.com/intl/ja/policies/privacy/) If you delete your cookies, use a different browser or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.
